<resources xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<string key="1403_Topic1_Prompt">La plaga</string>
	<string key="1403_Topic1_Response">La plaga es una maldición de la tierra y, por ende, lo es también del cuerpo. Las alimañas de la Arboleda del Edén son víctimas de ella, pero la plaga también afecta al cuerpo humano. La plaga te debilita y te acerca a la muerte con cada respiración. Ten cuidado y prepara una buena defensa contra ella cuando visites las zonas infectas de la Arboleda del Edén.</string>
	<string key="1425_Prospector_talk_Prompt" speaker="UI - player prompt">«Eh... ¿Qué es un Asalto a puesto remoto?».</string>
	<string key="1425_Prospector_talk_Response" speaker="ProspectorDelgado" name="ProspectorDelgado" VO="1425_Prospector_talk_Response" VO_Status="Recorded">El Asalto a puesto remoto es un enfrentamiento de 20 vs. 20 que se lleva a cabo en una extensa isla con tres puestos remotos.\nLos jugadores compiten por capturarlos y defenderlos el mayor tiempo posible para aumentar la puntuación de su equipo.</string>
	<string key="1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist01_Prompt" speaker="UI - player prompt" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">"I am looking for someone, actually."</string>
	<string key="1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist01_Response" speaker="Cultist Akech - Edengrove" gender="Male" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">Oh? Well, I am afraid I cannot help you there. I arrived only this morning and I do not know a single name!</string>
	<string key="1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist02_Prompt" speaker="UI - player prompt" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">"Will any other newcomers be there?"</string>
	<string key="1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist02_Response" speaker="Cultist Ylva - Edengrove" gender="Female" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">Well… we did have one young woman at our table last night, but I am not certain if she will choose to stay. If you ask me, she seemed rather attached to her mother.</string>
	<string key="1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist03_Prompt" speaker="UI - player prompt" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">"Have you met a young woman named Han Liu?"</string>
	<string key="1427_0101_TalkTo_Cultist03_Response" speaker="Cultist Jalair - Edengrovr" gender="Male" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">I have. Is she a friend of yours? You might want to speak to the High Seer if you would like to join her. I believe she departed for her walk in the dark hours of the morning.</string>
	<string key="1427_0101_TalkTo_CultOfficer_Prompt" speaker="UI - player prompt" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">"I am looking for a woman named Han Liu."</string>
	<string key="1427_0101_TalkTo_CultOfficer_Response" speaker="Agnes Cubert - Edengrove" gender="Female" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">Ah, Miss Liu. A promising young spark, that one. She walks the path of truth now. If she returns, I am sure she will be glad to see you after such a trial. We all eagerly await the outcome of her communion.</string>
	<string key="1427_0102_TalkTo_CultOfficer_Pilgrimmage_Prompt" speaker="UI - player prompt" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">"I'm ready to learn more."</string>
	<string key="1427_0102_TalkTo_CultOfficer_Pilgrimmage_Response" speaker="Agnes Cubert - Edengrove" gender="Female" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">I can tell you, or you can see for yourself. Follow the path to the south as it mounts the peak. Imbue these seeds in a great temple's waters and plant them in soft soil.\n\nIf you are swift, you may join Miss Liu.</string>
	<string key="1427_0102_TalkTo_Oath_Prompt" speaker="UI - player prompt" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">&lt;Speak the Oath.&gt;</string>
	<string key="1427_0102_TalkTo_Oath_Response" speaker="Oath Object" gender="None" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">"I stand before my fellows, humbled by nature's majesty.\n\nI came with many questions, and I seek only answers.\n\nI give myself to the unknown, in hopes of renewing my body and soul.\n\nWhat may be, will be."</string>
	<string key="1427_0102_TalkTo_Daughter_Umbrage_Prompt" speaker="UI - player prompt" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">"I'm not sure I am ready for this. Are you?"</string>
	<string key="1427_0102_TalkTo_Daughter_Umbrage_Response" speaker="Han Liu - Edengrove" gender="Female" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">I think so. I have read everything available to me in the enclave. I have spoken at length to the High Sage. I think I know enough about Umbrage to escape an unpleasant death there.\n\nAll the same… come with me?</string>
	<string key="1427_0104_TalkTo_CultMother_Prompt" speaker="UI - player prompt" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">"She survived, but she chose to join them."</string>
	<string key="1427_0104_TalkTo_CultMother_Response" speaker="Han Fang - Edengrove" gender="Female" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">It is as I feared.\n\nI have already asked so much of you… but could you stay with her? Convince them you intend to join as well? I cannot imagine leaving her alone with them. Her mind is so… malleable.</string>
	<string key="1427_0109_TalkTo_CultOfficer_Gold_Prompt" speaker="UI - player prompt" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">"Here is what I collected."</string>
	<string key="1427_0109_TalkTo_CultOfficer_Gold_Response" speaker="High Seer Agnes - Edengrove" gender="Female" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">Thank you. I have asked a great deal of you. It is time now for you to rest.\n\nGo now and meditate on all that you have seen.</string>
	<string key="1430_CultLeader_AboutCult_Prompt" speaker="Player Prompt" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">"Can you tell me more about this cult?"</string>
	<string key="1430_CultLeader_AboutCult_Response" speaker="The High Sage - Edengrove" gender="Male" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">If I were to write a pamphlet, I would wax eloquent about balance, simplicity, a life free from greed.\n\nBut you are here, among us. Stay. Share our meals. Listen to our stories. Our ways are open to any and all.</string>
	<string key="1430_CultLeader_AboutMask_Prompt" speaker="Player Prompt" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">"What's with the mask?"</string>
	<string key="1430_CultLeader_AboutMask_Response" speaker="The High Sage - Edengrove" gender="Male" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">I have a profoundly ugly face.\n\nNo, pardon my jest. I chose this mask to reinforce that I am nothing, indeed I am no ONE, but a conduit for the ethos of the Cult. It matters not who I am, only what I may offer.</string>
	<string key="1430_CultLeader_HighSage_Prompt" speaker="Player Prompt" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">"Are you the High Sage?"</string>
	<string key="1430_CultLeader_HighSage_Response" speaker="The High Sage - Edengrove" gender="Male" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">I am, though it is not a title I would have chosen for myself. I was drawn here, just like the others, but I feel I have come closest to articulating why.\n\nPerhaps that is why they chose me.</string>
	<string key="1431_0103_TalkTo_Innkeeper_Prompt" speaker="UI - player prompt" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">"Lilian said you could give me a drink…?"</string>
	<string key="1431_0103_TalkTo_Innkeeper_Response" speaker="Innkeeper Yatim- Edengrove" gender="Male" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">I take it they ah… stepped out… as it were. Here, go on, I'll put it on their tab.</string>
	<string key="1434_0104_TalkTo_Dryad_Prompt" speaker="UI - player prompt" rel_version="Quest_Supplement_Edengrove">"Are you Ranger Yasin's 'Love'?"</string>
	<string key="1434_0104_TalkTo_Dryad_Response" speaker="Dryad Hedera - Edengrove" gender="Female">Puede que él crea que lo soy. Mis flores a veces tienen ese efecto en los seres humanos. Lo recogeré.\n\nLa cura es repugnante, pero efectiva. Recoge algo de plaga y tráela a mi gruta. Te la marcaré en el mapa.</string>
</resources>

